Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Anarchism Serials TAM.766
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Le Reveil Anarchiste: Le Reveil Anarchiste, Geneva, Switzerland, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Leef in Chaos: Groningen, Netherlands, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Leveler: Fire Ant Collective, Insurgency Collective, Los Angeles, CA, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Libera Volo: Federacio Anarkiista, Hiroshima, Japan, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Liberacion: Colectivo Liberacion, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Libertaire: Japan, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 4, Box 53, Folder 5)
- Libertaria: Rome, Italy, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Libertarian: Toronto Libertarian Group, Ontario, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Libertarian Book Club: Libertarian Book Club, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Libertarian Quarterly: Libertarian Publishers, Ltd., Bombay, India, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Libertarian Struggle: Anarchists Workers Association, Leeds, UK, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Libertarian Vanguard: Radical Caucus of the Libertarian Party, San Francisco, CA, 1979-1982 (Box 16, Folder 9, Box 39, Folder 4-5)
- Libertarian Workers Bulletin: Libertarian Workers for a Self-Managed Society, Melbourne, Australia, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 10, Box 39, Folder 6-10, Box 54, Folder 7)
- Libertarian World: Libertarian Socialist League, Los Angeles, CA, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Liberte Anarchistisches Magazin, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Liberty: Liberty, Fort Montgomery, NY, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 2, Box 39, Folder 12)
- Lomakatsi: Lomakatsi, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Lone Wolf: Washington, DC, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Looking Forward!: Stelton Anarchist Youth, Stelton, NJ, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Lucha Libertaria: La Federacion Anarquista Uruguaya, Montevideo, Uruguay, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Lutter!: Union des Travailleurs Communistes Libertaires, Paris, France, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Machinery of Conformity: Friends of Malatesta, Buffalo, NY, Undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Manifeste: Organisation Socialiste Libertaire, Geneva, Switzerland, Undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Martello: Libertario Fondato da Carlo Tresca, New York, NY, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Match!: Student Liberation Action Movement, Tucson, AZ, 1971-1993 (Box 16, Folder 19-20, Box 17, Folder 1, Box 39, Folder 15-18)
- Match!: Pamphlet Series: Student Liberation Action Movement, Tucson, AZ, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Materialismo e Liberta, 1945-1963 (Box 17, Folder 3, Box 39, Folder 19)
- Media de AS: Netherlands, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Merseyside Anarchist Newsletter: Liverpool Anarchist Group, Liverpool, UK, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Miscelaneas Libertarias, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Motin: Mexico City, Mexico, Undated (Box 17, Folder 7, Box 54, Folder 8)
- Multual Aid Alternatives: Mutual Aid Collective, Albany, NY, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Negativite de L'Anarchisme: Texte Traduit de la Revue "Interrogations", Paris, France, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Nervio: Paris, France, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- New Formulation: The New Formulation, San Diego, CA, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- New Spur: Guy A. Aldred, Glasgow, Scotland, 1934 (Box Shared Tamiment 063, Folder 13)
- News From Nowhere: News From Nowhere, Eugene, OR, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Newsletter of the Organisation of Revolutionary Archivists: Organisation of Revolutionary Anarchists, Heslington, UK, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Noir Papier Anarchist: France, Undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
- North American Anarchist: Anarchist Communist Federation of North America, Toronto, Ontario, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 13, Box 39, Folder 23)
- Nosotras: Colectivo "Mujeres Libertarias Emma Goldman", Mexico, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Nosotras: Grupo Latino Americano de Mujers, Paris, France, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Nosotros: Valencia, Spain, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Nueva Senda: La F.I.J.L. en el Exilio, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- O ANAPXIKOΣ, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 17, Box 53, Folder 7)
- Obrer Prisioner: Los Pres@s Anaquistas en Lucha, Madrid, Spain, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 21, Box 54, Folder 9)
- Oh Dear, Not Again: Serendipity, Undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Open Road: Emma Goldman Papers, Berkeley, CA, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Open Road: Open Road, Vancouver, BC, 1976-1988 (Box 40, Folder 3-7)
- Organizer: Industrial Workers of the World - Twin Cities General Membership Branch, Minneapolis, MN, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Orto: Revista Cultural de Ideas Acratas: ORTO y Ediciones S. C. Ltda, Barcelona, Spain, 1993-2008 (Box 20, Folder 2, Folder 10-11, Box 21, Folder 1-4, Box 22, Folder 1-5, Box 23, Folder 1-3)
- Pamphlet series: Organisation of Revolutionary Anarchists, Undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Pensee et Action: Paris, France, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Pensiero e Volonta: Società Anon. Poligrafica Italiana, Rome, Italy, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
- Perennial Books: John Petrovato and Chris Halls, Montague, MA, Undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Plain Words: Paterson Anarchist Collective, Haledon, NJ, Undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Project 1313: Project 1313, Lawrence, KS, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Propaganda: @Front, New York, NY, Undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
- R.A.S.H Update: Red and Anarchist Skin Heads, New York, NY, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- RAGE!: MAYDAY Network of Anarchists, Decatur, GA, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Raven: Anarchists in Eastern Europe: Freedom Press, London, UK, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Reality Now: Anti-Authoritarian News Network, Toronto, Ontario, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Rebel!: SRAFprint Co-op, Santa Rosa, CA, Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Red & Black: Anarchist and Communist Federation of North America, Chicago, IL, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Red & Black: Sydney University Anarchists, Sydney, Australia, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Red Libertaria: Prensa Anarquista: Red Libertaria APOYO MUTUO, Madrid, Spain, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Revolutionary Almanac: The Rabelais Press, New York, NY, 1914 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Revolutionary Cause: August 29th Movement, San Francisco, CA, 1975-1978 (Box 41, Folder 3-6)
- Revuelta: Grupo Revuelta, Barcelona, Spain, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Rojo y Negro: Confederación General del Trabajo (España), Madrid, Spain, 1999-2002 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Sabotaje: Madrid, Spain, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- SAC Newsletter: Syndicalists - Central Organization of Swedish Workers, Stockholm, Sweden, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Sawblade: Sawblade Collective, New York, NY, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Self Management Newsletter: Resurgence, Evanston, IL, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Senzapatria: Sondrio, Milan, Italy, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Sicilia Libertaria: Associazione Culturale Sicilia Punto L, Ragusa, Italy, 1997-2003 (Box 27, Folder 3-8)
- Simiente Libertaria: El Grupo Libertario "Errico Malatesta", Caracas, Venezuela, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Sindicalismo: Organo de la Federacion Sindicalista Libertaria, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Siren Newsletter: Anarchist Women's Group, Venice, CA, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Slingshot: Slingshot Newspaper/Long Haul, Berkeley, CA, 1989-2006 (Box 19, Folder 6, Box 41, Folder 12)
- Smash Apathy: Smash Apathy, Fairlawn, NJ, 1980-1989 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Sociaal-Democratie en Anarchisme: Sociaaldemocratische Arbeiderspatij in Netherland (SDAP), Amsterdam, Netherlands, Undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Social Ecology Network International: Institute for Social Ecology, Plainfield, VT, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Social Monster: Internationale Bibliothek, New York, NY, 1890 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Spain and the World: Thos. H. Keell, London, UK, 1936-1937 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Sparks: Anarcho-Syndicalist Transport Workers Paper, Moreland, Australia, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- SRAF Bulletin:, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- State Adversary: The State Adversary, Wellington, NZ, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Stuff It: Bristol Anarchist Group, Bristol, UK, Undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Svobodna Misul: Federation of Anarchists in Bulgaria, Sofia, Bulgaria, 1992-1995 (Box Shared Tamiment 061, Folder 8-10)
- Taking Liberties: Anarchist Black Cross, London, UK, Undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Terra Lliure: Regional Catalana CNT, Paris, France, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Terre Libre, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- TESAO: Coletivo Anarquista Branca-leone, Sao Paolo, Brazil, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Tinta Negra: Sindicat D'Informacio i Arts Grafiques CNT-AIT, Barcelona, Spain, 1982-1995 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Towards Anarchism: Order in Freedom: The Libertarian League, New York, NY, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Trade Winds, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Traffico: Rome, Italy, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Trafik: Mulheim, Germany, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Umanità Nova: Federazione Anarchica Italiana, Rome, Italy, 1992-2007 (Box 42, Folder 1-6, Box 43, Folder 1-7, Box 44, Folder 1-5, Box 45, Folder 1-8, Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Box 50, Box 51, Folder 1-9, Box Shared Tamiment 047, Folder 12-15, Box 54, Folder 10-12)
- Under Currents: Under Currents, Santa Cruz, CA, Undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Utopian Anarchist Party: Utopian Anarchist Party, Silver Spring, MD, Undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Utopian: A Journal of Anarchism and Libertarian Socialism: The Utopian Publishing, Co., New York, NY, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Vital Information: Vital Information, New Orleans, LA, Undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Voce Libertaria: Amici dell'Adunata, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 15, Box 54, Folder 13)
- Voices of Reason: NYU Objectivist Club, New York, NY, Undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Voluntad: La Agrupacion Anarquista, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Voz Anarquista: Centro de Cultura Libertaria, Portugal, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- When Gendarme Sleeps! (Anarchy's Zine of Poetry), 2001 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Wobbly City: NYC Industrial Workers of the World, New York, NY, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Writing on the Wall: The Newspaper Project, Chicago, IL, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Yatte Nai Ore o Mokugeki Dekiru Ka!: Mori o Mamoru Kai, 1986 (Box Shared Tamiment 062, Folder 1)
- Yow-Anarchy Comics: Anarchy Comics, San Francisco, CA, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Zendik Farm Tribe: Zendik Farm, Boulevard, CA, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Zero: Zero Collective, London, UK, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Zyntoma: Mexico City, Mexico, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 9)